<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MadMeme</title>
    <link>https://madmeme.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MadMeme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://madmeme.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adjective</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/info/adjective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/info/adjective/</guid>
      <description>In linguistics, an adjective (abbreviated adj) is a word that modifies a noun or noun phrase or describes its referent. Its semantic role is to change information given by the noun.
Adjectives are one of the main parts of speech of the English language, although historically they were classed together with nouns. Certain words that were traditionally considered to be adjectives, including the, this, my, etc., are today usually classed separately, as determiners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grammatical person</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/info/grampers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/info/grampers/</guid>
      <description>In linguistics, grammatical person is the grammatical distinction between deictic references to participant(s) in an event; typically the distinction is between the speaker (first person), the addressee (second person), and others (third person). First person includes the speaker (English: I, we, me, and us), second person is the person or people spoken to (English: you), and third person includes all that is not listed above (English: she, he, they, etc.) Grammatical person typically defines a language&amp;rsquo;s set of personal pronouns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noun</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/info/noun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/info/noun/</guid>
      <description>A noun (from Latin nōmen, literally &amp;lsquo;name&amp;rsquo;) is a word that functions as the name of a specific object or set of objects, such as living creatures, places, actions, qualities, states of existence, or ideas. However, noun is not a semantic category, so that it cannot be characterized in terms of its meaning. Thus, actions and states of existence can also be expressed by verbs, qualities by adjectives, and places by adverbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time of the Day</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/info/timeofday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/info/timeofday/</guid>
      <description>Afternoon is the time of the day between noon and evening. It is the time when the sun is descending from its peak in the sky to somewhat before its terminus at the horizon in the west. In human life, it occupies roughly the latter half of the standard work and school day. In literal terms, it refers to a time specifically after noon. The equivalent of Earth&amp;rsquo;s afternoon on another planet would refer to the time the principal star of that planetary system would be in descent from its prime meridian, as seen from the planet&amp;rsquo;s surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verb</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/info/verb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/info/verb/</guid>
      <description>A verb, from the Latin verbum meaning word, is a word (part of speech) that in syntax conveys an action (bring, read, walk, run, learn), an occurrence (happen, become), or a state of being (be, exist, stand). In the usual description of English, the basic form, with or without the particle to, is the infinitive.
In many languages, verbs are inflected (modified in form) to encode tense, aspect, mood, and voice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warum geht Paulchen Brötchen holen?</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/warum-geht-paulchen-broetchen-holen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/warum-geht-paulchen-broetchen-holen/</guid>
      <description>Warum geht Paulchen Brötchen holen?  Aufgabe 1 Lies die Geschichte. Dann kannst du die Frage, warum Paulchen Brötchen holt, beantworten. In der Geschichte fehlen allerdings noch Wörter. Du musst die richtigen Wörter auswählen und einsetzen. Dabei ist es wichtig, dass du den Kontext der Geschichte verstehst. Viel Spaß!
  ?1 Paulchen will heute wieder unbedingt Brötchen beim  holen. Die Mutter wundert sich über seinen Ehrgeiz, während sie den  deckt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>