<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> ParaText on ParaText</title>
    <link>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  ParaText on ParaText</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Der schlaue Fuchs</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/der-schlaue-fuchs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/der-schlaue-fuchs/</guid>
      <description>Der schlaue Fuchs  In the following a german text is presented.
 Click here!
 Click the element in order to interact with the text!
 Each italicword in the text can be clicked.
 Try it out now and click the words above.
 Several interactions are hidden. Have fun! :-)
 Continue?   However, the text contains riddles.
 Only if all riddles isareamissolved, the boringpreviousnextboringparagraph is shown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Du deklinierst ein Verb</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/declinate-verbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/declinate-verbs/</guid>
      <description>Du deklinierst ein Verb   Choose a verb&amp;ldquo; Select a verb!gehenlaufenmachenzeigeneinkaufen&amp;rdquo;!
    An english translationof the verb is to Input translation!gogorundoshowshop.
 Select one meaningful translation!   Declination always takes place with a pronounand a verb. The german decilnationdepends on singular (sg.) and plural (pl.). Does the phrase Select an Example!ich laufedu l채ufster l채uftsie l채uftes l채uftwir laufenihr lauftsie laufenich gehedu gehster gehtsie gehtes gehtwir gehenihr gehtsie gehenich machedu machster machtsie machtes machtwir machenihr machtsie machenich zeigedu zeigster zeigtsie zeigtes zeigtwir zeigenihr zeigtsie zeigenich kaufe eindu kaufst einer kauft einsie kauft eines kauft einwir kaufen einihr kauft einsie kaufen eincorresponds to one of the possible declinations of the verb ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ParaText Documentation</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/paratext-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/paratext-docs/</guid>
      <description>ParaText Documentation  Paragraphs  Paragraph Alignment Alignment can be done using one of the following codes at the beginning of a pragraph.
 &amp;lt;&amp;lt;: left-aligned &amp;gt;&amp;gt;: right-aligned &amp;lt;&amp;gt;: justified &amp;gt;&amp;lt;: centered   Continue?   Text and Narrator Paragraphs Text Paragraphs can be defined using --- on a single line. Each element in one text paragragph has to be figured out in order for the next text paragraph to appear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Separable Prefix Verbs</title>
      <link>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/separable-prefix-verbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://madmeme.github.io/paratext/separable-prefix-verbs/</guid>
      <description>Separable Prefix Verbs  German seems complex, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually really easy. Let&amp;rsquo;s start practising Separable prefix verbs (SPV). I&amp;rsquo;ll show you. You will get it really quick.
 Each italicword in the text can be clicked.
 Try it out now and click the words above.
 Continue?   SPV are simply verbs that can separate. They consist of:
 a prefixand a verbstem For example:
 einkaufen ankommen aufwachen   Are you ready for your first task?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>